A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, China Medical Board records, RG 4 FA114
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appropriations, 1913-1929; 1
  - Appropriations - Numerical, 1913-1918; 1
    - 241. American Friends Mission Hospital - Nanking, Kiangsu, 1914-15 (Box 21, Folder 415)
    - 242. University of Nanking - Nanking, Kiangsu, 1914-18 (Box 21, Folder 416)
    - 242. University of Nanking - Nanking, Kiangsu, 1914-18 (Box 21, Folder 417)
    - 242. University of Nanking - Nanking, Kiangsu, 1914-18 (Box 21, Folder 418)
    - 242.2 University of Nanking - Statistics, Reports (Box 21, Folder 419)
    - 243. Chinese Public Isolation Hospital - Shanghai, Kiangsu, 1914 (Box 22, Folder 420)
    - 244. Cholera Hospital of the Chinese Red Cross Society - Shanghai, Kiangsu, 1914 (Box 22, Folder 421)
    - 245. Kiangsu Provincial Medical School - Soochow, Kiangsu, 1914 (Box 22, Folder 422)
    - 246. Women's Union Mission Hospital - Shaghai, Kiangsu, 1914-18 (Box 22, Folder 423)
    - 247. Municipal Health Laboratories - Shanghai, Kiangsu, 1914 (Box 22, Folder 424)
    - 248. American Church Mission Hospital - Shanghai, Kiangsu, 1914-18 (Box 22, Folder 425)
      Protestant Episcopal Church in U.S.
    - 249. Shanghai American School - Shanghai, Kiangsu, 1916-18 (Box 22, Folder 426)
      Educate American Children
    - 250. Harvard Medical School of China - Shanghai, Kiangsu, 1913-18 (Box 22, Folder 427)
    - 250. Harvard Medical School of China - Shanghai, Kiangsu, 1913-18 (Box 22, Folder 428)
    - 250. Harvard Medical School of China - Shanghai, Kiangsu, 1913-18 (Box 22, Folder 429)
    - 250. Harvard Medical School of China - Shanghai, Kiangsu, 1913-18 (Box 22, Folder 430)
    - 250.2 Reports, 1914-16 (Box 22, Folder 431)
    - 250.3 Roger Roger Clapp, 1916 (Box 22, Folder 432)
    - 250.4 Staff, 1916-18 (Box 22, Folder 433)
    - 250.5 Fellowships, 1916-18 (Box 22, Folder 434)
    - 250.5 Fellowships, 1916-18 (Box 22, Folder 435)
    - 251. Shanghai Baptist College - Shanghai, Kiangsu, 1915-18 (Box 22, Folder 436)
    - 252. Shanghai General Hospital - Shanghai, Kiangsu, 1914 (Box 22, Folder 437)
      British firm
    - 253. Shantung Road Hospital - Shanghai, Kiangsu, 1914 (Box 23, Folder 438)
      London Missionary Society
    - 254. St. John's University, Shanghai, Kiangsu, 1914-18 (Box 23, Folder 439)
      Christian Association of the University of Pennsylvania
    - 254. St. John's University, Shanghai, Kiangsu, 1914-18 (Box 23, Folder 440)
    - 254.2 Statistics (Box 23, Folder 441)
    - 255.2 Shanghai Medical School - Proposals (Box 23, Folder 442)
      Harvard
    - 255.8 Statistics (Box 23, Folder 443)
    - 256. Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital (South) - Soochow, Kiangsu, 1914-18 (Box 23, Folder 444)
    - 257. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (South) - Soochow, Kiangsu, 1915-16 (Box 23, Folder 445)
    - 258. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Soochow, Kiangsu, 1914 (Box 23, Folder 446)
    - 259. Foreign Christian Missionary Society Hospital - Nantungchow, Kiangsu, 1915-18 (Box 23, Folder 447)
    - 260. American Church Mission Hospital - Wusih, Kiangsu, 1914-16 (Box 23, Folder 448)
    - 261. Southern Baptist Convention Mission Hospital - Yangshow, Kiangsu, 1915-18 (Box 23, Folder 449)
    - 262. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Yu Yiao, Kiangsu, 1914 (Box 23, Folder 450)
    - 263. Zangsok Dispensary - Zangzok, Kiangsu, 1914 (Box 23, Folder 451)
    - 264. Church Missionary Society Hospital - Kweilin, Kwangsi, 1914 (Box 23, Folder 452)
    - 265. Southern Baptist Convention Mission Hospital - Wuchow, Kwangsi, 1914-17 (Box 23, Folder 453)
    - 266. Wesleyan Methodist Mission Hospital - Wuchow, Kwangsi, 1914 (Box 23, Folder 454)
    - 267. Soochow University - Soochow, Kiangsu, 1916-18 (Box 23, Folder 455)
      Methodist Episcopal Church (South)
    - 270. Canton Christian College, Canton Hospital - Canton, Kwantung, 1914 - May 1915 (Box 23, Folder 456)
      Interdenominational. J. Oscar Thomson
    - 270. Canton Christian College, Canton Hospital - Canton, Kwantung, 1914 - May 1915 (Box 23, Folder 457)
    - 270. Canton Christian College, Canton Hospital - Canton, Kwantung, June 1915-18 (Box 24, Folder 458)
    - 270. Canton Christian College, Canton Hospital - Canton, Kwantung, June 1915-18 (Box 24, Folder 459)
    - 270. Canton Christian College, Canton Hospital - Canton, Kwantung, June 1915-18 (Box 24, Folder 460)
    - 271. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Canton, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 461)
    - 272. Hospital Doumer - Canton, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 462)
      French Government
    - 273. John G. Kerr Hospital for the Insane - Canton, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 463)
    - 274. Kwong Hua Hospital - Canton, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 464)
    - 275. Kung Yee Medical School and Hospital - Canton, Kwantung, 1913-15 (Box 24, Folder 465)
      Chinese Gentlemen
    - 276. American Baptist Mission Hospital (North) - Chaochow, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 466)
    - 277. English Presbyterian Mission Hospital - Chaochow, Kwantung, 1914-18 (Box 24, Folder 467)
    - 278. American Baptist Mission Hospital (North) - Chaoyang, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 468)
    - 279. Wesleyan Methodist Mission Hospital - Fatshan, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 469)
    - 280. London Missionary Society Hospital - Hong Kong, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 470)
    - 281. Hong Kong University Medical School - Hong Kong, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 471)
    - 282. Tung Wah Hospital - Hong Kong, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 472)
    - 283. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Kachek, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 473)
    - 284. American Baptist Mission Hospital (North) - Kityang, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 474)
    - 285. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Kiungchow, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 475)
    - 286. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Kochow, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 476)
    - 287. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Lienchow, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 477)
    - 288. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Nodoa (Hainan), Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 478)
    - 289. Church Missionary Society Hospital - Pakhoi, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 479)
    - 290. English Presbyterian Mission Hospital - Samhopa, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 480)
    - 291. Wesleyan Methodist Mission Hospital - shiuchow, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 481)
    - 292. English Presbyterian Mission Hospital - Swahue, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 482)
    - 293. English Presbyterian Mission Hospital - Swatow, Kwantung, 1914-18 (Box 24, Folder 483)
    - 294. American Baptist Mission Hospital (North) - Swatow, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 484)
    - 295. United Brethren Hospital - Siulan, Kwantung, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 485)
      Foreign Missionary Society
    - 296. English Presbyterian Mission Hospital - Wukingfu, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 486)
    - 297. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Yeungkong, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 487)
    - 298. Southern Baptist Convention Mission Hospital - Yingtak, Kwantung, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 488)
    - 299. United Free Church of Scotland Mission Hospital - Ashiho, Manchuria, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 489)
    - 300. United Free Church of Scotland Mission Hospital - Chaoyangchen, Manchuria, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 490)
    - 301. Irish Presbyterian Mission Hospital - Chinchowfu, Manchuria, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 491)
    - 302. Irish Presbyterian Mission Hospital - Fakumen, Manchuria, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 492)
    - 303. Irish Presbyterian Mission Hospital - Sinminfu, Manchuria, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 493)
    - 304. United Free Church of Scotland Mission Hospital - Hulan, Manchuria, 1914-15 (Box 24, Folder 494)
    - 305. United Free Church of Scotland Mission Hospital - Kaiyuan, Manchuria, 1914-15 (Box 24, Folder 495)
    - 306. Irish Presbyterian Mission Hospital - Kirin, Manchuria, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 496)
    - 307. Irish Presbyterian Mission Hospital - Kwanchengtze, Manchuria, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 497)
    - 308. United Free Church of Scotland Mission Hospital - Liaoyang, Manchuria, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 498)
    - 309. United Free Church of Scotland Mission Hospital - Moukden, Manchura, 1914-18 (Box 24, Folder 499)
    - 310. School for Blind Chinese Girls - Moukden, Manchuria, 1914-15 (Box 24, Folder 500)
      Interdenominational
    - 311. United Free Church of Scotland Mission Hospital - Tiehling, Manchuria, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 501)
    - 312. United Free Church of Scotland Mission Hospital - Yungling, Manchuria, 1914 (Box 24, Folder 502)
    - 313. Church of Brethren Mission Hospital - Pingtingchow, Shansi, 1917-18 (Box 24, Folder 503)
    - 316. English Baptist Mission Hospital - Taiyuan, Shansi, 1914-17 (Box 25, Folder 504)
    - 317. Shansi Province, 1915 (Box 25, Folder 505)
    - 318. American Board Mission Hospital - Fenchow, Shansi, 1914-18 (Box 25, Folder 506)
      Congregational
    - 319. China Inland Mission Hospital - Pingyangfu, Shansi, 1914 (Box 25, Folder 507)
    - 320. English Baptist Mission Hospital - Taichow, Shansi, 1914-15 (Box 25, Folder 508)
    - 321. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Chefoo, Shantung, 1914-18 (Box 25, Folder 509)
    - 322. China Inland Mission Hospital - Chefoo, Shantung, 1914 (Box 25, Folder 510)
    - 323. Southern Baptist Convention Mission Hospital - Hwangsien, Shantung, 1914-18 (Box 25, Folder 511)
    - 324. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Ichowfu, Shantung, 1914-16 (Box 25, Folder 512)
    - 325. Southern Baptist Convention Mission Mospital - Laichow, Shantung, 1914-15 (Box 25, Folder 513)
    - 326. American Board Mission Hospital - Lintsing, Shantung, 1914-16 (Box 25, Folder 514)
    - 327. American Board Mission Hospital - Pangchwang, Shantung, 1914 (Box 25, Folder 515)
    - 328. Peichen Hospital - Peichen, Shantung, 1914 (Box 25, Folder 516)
      English Baptist Mission
    - 329. Southern Baptist Convention Hospital - Pingtu, Shantung, 1914-16 (Box 25, Folder 517)
    - 330. Church of England Mission Hospital Pingtu, Shantung, 1914 (Box 25, Folder 0517A)
      Society for Propagation of the Gospel
    - 331. Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital (North) - Tainfu, Shantung, 1914-15 (Box 25, Folder 518)
    - 332. American Board Mission Hospital - Tehchow, Shantung, 1915-18 (Box 25, Folder 519)
    - 333. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Tengchow, Shantung, 1914-15 (Box 25, Folder 520)
    - 334. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Tsinanfu, Shantung, 1914-16 (Box 25, Folder 521)
    - 335. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Tsining, Shantung, 1914-16 (Box 25, Folder 522)
    - 336. English Baptist Mission Hospital - Tsingchowfu, Shantung, 1914-5 (Box 25, Folder 523)
    - 337. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Tsingtao, Shantung, 1914 (Box 25, Folder 524)
    - 338. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Weihsien, Shantung, 1914-16 (Box 25, Folder 525)
    - 339. Church of England Mission Hospital - Yenchowfu, Shantung, 1914 (Box 25, Folder 526)
      Society for the Propagation of the Gospel
    - 340. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Yihsien, Shantung, 1914-16 (Box 25, Folder 527)
    - 341. English Baptist Mission Hospital - Tsowping, Shantung, 1914 (Box 25, Folder 528)
    - 342. Southern Baptist Convention Mission Hospital - Laiyang, Shantung, 1915-16 (Box 25, Folder 529)
    - 343. Presbyterian Mission Hospital (North) - Tenghsien, Shantung, 1916 (Box 25, Folder 530)
    - 344. Church of Brethren Mission Hospital - Liaochu, Shantung, 1918 (Box 25, Folder 531)
    - 352. Union Medical College - Tsinan, Shantung, 1914-16 (Box 25, Folder 532)
      Medical School for Shantung Christian University - J. B. Neal
    - 352. Union Medical College - Tsinan, Shantung, 1917-18 (Box 26, Folder 533)
    - 352. Union Medical College - Tsinan, Shantung, 1917-18 (Box 26, Folder 534)
    - 352.2 Statistics (Box 26, Folder 535)
    - 353. Shantung Christian University - Tsinan, Shantung, 1914-18 (Box 26, Folder 536)
    - 354. English Baptist Mission Hospital - Sianfu, Shensi, 1914-17 (Box 26, Folder 537)
    - 355. Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital (North) - Chengtu, Szechwan, 1914-15 (Box 26, Folder 538)
    - 356. Methodist Episcopal Mission Hospital (North) - Chungking, Szechwan, 1914-16 (Box 26, Folder 539)
    - 357. American Baptist Mission Hospital (North) - Kiating, Szechwan, 1914 (Box 26, Folder 540)
    - 358. China Inland Mission Hospital - Kienchow, Szechwan, 1914 (Box 26, Folder 541)
    - 359. Church Missionary Society Hospital - Mienchuhsien, Szechwan, 1914-15 (Box 26, Folder 542)
    - 362. Friends Foreign Mission Association Hospital - Suining, Szechwan, 1914-17 (Box 26, Folder 543)
    - 363. Friends Foreign Mission Association Hospital - Tungchwan, Szechwan, 1914 (Box 26, Folder 544)
    - 364. American Baptist Mission Hospital (North) - Yachow, Szechwan, 1914 (Box 26, Folder 545)
    - 365. Union College - Ningpo, Chekiang, 1916 (Box 26, Folder 546)
      Proposal
    - 366. American Board Mission Hospital - Taikuhsien, Shanoi, 1914-18 (Box 26, Folder 547)
    - 368. Canadian Methodist Mission Hospital - Chengtu, Szechwan, 1918 (Box 26, Folder 548)
    - 369. Nankai School - Tientsing, Chihli, 1916 (Box 26, Folder 549)
      Chinese. Chang Poling
    - 370. Peiyang University - Tientsin, Hunan, 1919 (Box 26, Folder 550)
    - 372. Tuberculosis Sanatorium - Changsha, Hunan, 1919 (Box 26, Folder 551)
      Chinese Red Cross
    - 373. Church Missionary Society Hospital - Yunnanfu, Yunnan, 1917 (Box 26, Folder 552)
    - 374.2 Missionary Society of the Church of England in Canada - Paul V. Helliwell, 1917-18 (Box 26, Folder 553)
    - 375. Severance Union Medical College - Seoul, Korea, 1914-15 (Box 26, Folder 554)
    - 376. Free Methodist Church of North America, 1918 (Box 26, Folder 555)
    - 377. Foreign Mission Conference of North America, 1915-18 (Box 26, Folder 556)
      James L. Barton. Higher Christian Education; Survey
    - 378.2 American Advent Missional Society - Charles A. Powell, 1918 (Box 26, Folder 557)
    - 400. Formosa, 1918 (Box 26, Folder 558)
    - 405. Japan, 1914-15 (Box 26, Folder 559)
      St. Luke's Hospital, Waseda University, Imperial University Medical School, Kyoto University Hospital, Kyoto Prefectural Medical School.
    - 410. Korea, 1918 (Box 26, Folder 560)
    - 415. Philippine Islands, 1914 (Box 26, Folder 561)
      Philippine General Hospital, University of Philippines Medical School, Bureau of Science.
  - Appropriations - Alphabetical, 1919-1929; 2
    Subseries II is an alphabetical series in which administrative and general topics are mixed in with appropriations.
    Appropriations Index - Alphabetical
    A card index to China Medical Board records, Series 1.2: Appropriations – Alphabetical is available for use. Series 1.2 files are indicated by the file’s title (without an index number). The CMB Appropriations - Alphabetical Index cards are located in drawers 5-8 of the 72-drawer cabinet next to the RAC's reading room.
    - Accounts, 1923-28 (Box 27, Folder 562)
    - Accounts, 1923-28 (Box 27, Folder 563)
    - Accounts, 1923-28 (Box 27, Folder 564)
    - Accounts, 1923-28 (Box 27, Folder 565)
    - Accounts, 1923-28 (Box 27, Folder 566)
    - Accounts, 1923-28 (Box 27, Folder 567)
    - Accounts, 1923-28 (Box 27, Folder 568)
    - Advisory Committee on Chinese Student Affairs, 1924-25 (Box 27, Folder 569)
    - Advisory Committee on Higher Education in China, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 570)
    - John Agar, 1922-24 (Box 27, Folder 571)
    - Lucy Aldrich, 1923-26 (Box 27, Folder 572)
    - American Advent Mission Society, 1919 (Box 27, Folder 573)
    - American Advent Mission Hospital - Chaohsien, 1919 (Box 27, Folder 574)
    - American Baptist Foreign Mission Society, 1919-28 (Box 27, Folder 575)
      Political Situation. Labor contracts and unions, general strike.
    - American Baptist Foreign Mission Society, 1919-28 (Box 27, Folder 576)
    - American Baptist Mission Hospital - Ningpo, 1919-28 (Box 27, Folder 577)
    - American Baptist Mission Hospital - Ningpo, 1919-28 (Box 27, Folder 578)
    - American Baptist Mission Hospital - Shaosing, 1919-28 (Box 28, Folder 579)
    - American Baptist Mission Hospital - Shaosing, 1919-28 (Box 28, Folder 580)
    - American Baptist Mission Hospital - Siufu, 1919-21 (Box 28, Folder 581)
    - American Baptist Mission Hospital - Swatow, 1925 (Box 28, Folder 582)
    - American Baptist Mission Hospital - Yachow, 1919-23 (Box 28, Folder 583)
    - American Baptist Mission - Shanghai College, 1919-28 (Box 28, Folder 584)
    - American Baptist Mission - Shanghai College, 1919-28 (Box 28, Folder 585)
    - American Baptist Mission - Shanghai College, 1919-28 (Box 28, Folder 586)
    - American Baptist Mission - Shanghai College, 1919-28 (Box 28, Folder 587)
    - American Baptist Mission - Shanghai College, 1919-28 (Box 28, Folder 588)
    - American Baptist Mission - Shanghai College, 1919-28 (Box 28, Folder 589)
    - American Baptist Mission - Shanghai College, 1919-28 (Box 28, Folder 590)
    - American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions, 1919-28 (Box 29, Folder 591)
      Extraterritorial rights, famine, Generals Wu and Feng, plague.
    - American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions, 1919-28 (Box 29, Folder 592)
    - American Board Mission Hospital - Fenchow, 1920-28 (Box 29, Folder 593)
    - American Board Mission Hospital - Fenchow, 1920-28 (Box 29, Folder 594)
    - American Board Mission Hospital - Fenchow, 1920-28 (Box 29, Folder 595)
    - American Board Mission Hospital - Foochow, 1925 (Box 29, Folder 596)
    - American Board Mission Hospital - Taikuhsien, 1919-24 (Box 29, Folder 597)
    - American Board Mission Hospital - Techow, 1919-26 (Box 29, Folder 598)
    - American Board Mission Hospital - Techow, 1919-26 (Box 29, Folder 599)
    - American Board Mission Hospital - Techow, 1919-26 (Box 29, Folder 600)
    - American Board Mission Hospital - Techow, 1919-26 (Box 29, Folder 601)
    - American Board Mission Hospital - Tehchow, 1927-28 (Box 30, Folder 602)
    - American Board Mission Hospital - Tungchow, 1919-28 (Box 30, Folder 603)
    - American Academy of Political Science, 1927 (Box 30, Folder 604)
    - American Asiatic Association, 1919-25 (Box 30, Folder 605)
    - American Bible Society, 1927 (Box 30, Folder 606)
    - American Chamber of Commerce, Shanghai, 1923 (Box 30, Folder 607)
    - American Child Health Association, 1923 (Box 30, Folder 608)
    - American Chinese School, 1922-23 (Box 30, Folder 609)
    - American City Magazine, 1926 (Box 30, Folder 610)
    - American Committee on Coordination, 1926 (Box 30, Folder 611)
    - American Committee for Justice to China, 1925-28 (Box 30, Folder 612)
    - American Hospital Association, 1922 (Box 30, Folder 613)
    - American Institute in Peking, 1926-27 (Box 30, Folder 614)
    - American International Corporation, 1920-24 (Box 30, Folder 615)
    - American Journal of Science, 1924 (Box 30, Folder 616)
    - American Medical Association, 1922-28 (Box 30, Folder 617)
    - American Minister, 1922-25 (Box 30, Folder 618)
    - American Museum of Natural History, 1924 (Box 30, Folder 619)
    - American Public Health Organization, 1922-27 (Box 30, Folder 620)
    - American Red Cross, 1919-22 (Box 30, Folder 621)
    - American Relief Administration, 1922-23 (Box 30, Folder 622)
    - American Social Hygiene Association, 1924 (Box 30, Folder 623)
    - American Society of Mechanical Engineers, 1922 (Box 30, Folder 624)
    - American Women's Hospitals, 1926-27 (Box 30, Folder 625)
    - Amherst College, 1925 (Box 30, Folder 626)
    - Amoy University, 1923-28 (Box 30, Folder 627)
    - Amoy University, 1923-28 (Box 30, Folder 628)
    - Anatomy - Congdon, 1925 (Box 30, Folder 629)
    - Walter Anner, 1927 (Box 30, Folder 630)
    - Anti-narcotic Campaign, 1920-21 (Box 30, Folder 631)
    - Anti-plague Institute, 1927 (Box 30, Folder 632)
    - Antioch College, 1922-26 (Box 30, Folder 633)
    - Thomas B. Appleget, 1927-28 (Box 30, Folder 634)
    - Applications - Y. F. Chi, 1926 (Box 30, Folder 635)
    - Applications - K. C. Hsu, 1924 (Box 30, Folder 636)
    - Applications - R. S. Kidder, 1924 (Box 30, Folder 637)
    - Applications - A. R. Kilgore, 1919-20 (Box 30, Folder 638)
    - Applications - T. D. Lee, 1925 (Box 31, Folder 639)
    - Applications - Jeanne Magnet Logan, 1924-25 (Box 31, Folder 640)
    - Applications - S. C. Sung, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 641)
    - Applications - T. S. Wang, 1925 (Box 31, Folder 642)
    - Applications - Y. H. Woo, 1924-25 (Box 31, Folder 643)
    - Applications, 1919-26 (Box 31, Folder 644)
    - Applications, 1919-26 (Box 31, Folder 645)
    - Applications, 1919-26 (Box 31, Folder 646)
    - Applications, 1919-26 (Box 31, Folder 647)
    - Applications, 1919-26 (Box 31, Folder 648)
    - Applications, 1919-26 (Box 31, Folder 649)
    - Applications, 1919-26 (Box 31, Folder 650)
    - Appropriations, 1920-22 (Box 32, Folder 651)
    - Appropriations, 1920-22 (Box 32, Folder 652)
    - Architects - Butler & Rodman, 1919-20 (Box 32, Folder 653)
    - Architects - Coolidge & Shattuck, 1919-20 (Box 32, Folder 654)
    - Architects - Crow, Lewis & Wick, 1919-20 (Box 32, Folder 655)
    - Architects - McKim, Mead & White, 1919-20 (Box 32, Folder 656)
    - Architects - Schmidt, Garden & Martin, 1919-20 (Box 32, Folder 657)
    - Architects - Stevens & Lee, 1919-20 (Box 32, Folder 658)
    - Architects - York & Sawyer, 1919-20 (Box 32, Folder 659)
    - Architectural Service Bureau, 1918-24 (Box 32, Folder 660)
      Service to missionary organizations.
    - Architectural Service Bureau, 1918-24 (Box 32, Folder 661)
    - Architectural Service Bureau, 1918-24 (Box 32, Folder 662)
    - Architectural Service Bureau, 1925-28 (Box 33, Folder 663)
    - Architectural Service Bureau, 1925-28 (Box 33, Folder 664)
    - M. F. Arbuckle, 1922 (Box 33, Folder 665)
    - Archaeology, 1922-24 (Box 33, Folder 666)
    - Army Medical College, 1920-23 (Box 33, Folder 667)
    - Armitage Memorial Fund, 1919-25 (Box 33, Folder 668)
    - Julian Arnold, 1923-27 (Box 33, Folder 669)
    - Asia Publishing Company, 1927 (Box 33, Folder 670)
    - Asiatic Monthly, 1920-22 (Box 33, Folder 671)
    - Association of American Colleges, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 672)
    - Association of Chinese and American Engineers, 1922 (Box 33, Folder 673)
    - Association for the Welfare of Children in China, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 674)
    - Atlantic Monthly, 1927 (Box 33, Folder 675)
    - Augustana Hospital, 1921-24 (Box 33, Folder 676)
    - T. H. Auyong, 1922 (Box 33, Folder 677)
    - E. Carleton Baker, 1920-27 (Box 33, Folder 678)
    - Baltimore Department of Health, 1921 (Box 33, Folder 679)
    - Jessie Bannister, 1927 (Box 33, Folder 680)
    - Baptist Convention - Southern, 1919-25 (Box 33, Folder 681)
    - Baptist Mission Hospital (South) - Chengchow, 1921-25 (Box 33, Folder 682)
    - Baptist Mission Hospital (South) - Hwangsien, 1920-28 (Box 33, Folder 683)
    - Baptist Mission Hospital (South) - Kaifeng, 1922-23 (Box 33, Folder 684)
    - Baptist Mission Hospital (South) - Laichowfu, 1920-25 (Box 33, Folder 685)
    - Baptist Mission Hospital (South) - Pingtu, 1921-23 (Box 33, Folder 686)
    - Baptist Mission Hospital (South) - Yangchow, 1919-28 (Box 33, Folder 687)
    - Baptist Mission Hospital (South) - Yangchow, 1919-28 (Box 33, Folder 688)
    - Baptist Mission Hospital (South) - Wuchow, 1919-25 (Box 33, Folder 689)
    - Baptist Missionary Society (English), 1920-25 (Box 33, Folder 690)
    - Baptist Missionary Hospital (English) - Chowstun, 1922 (Box 33, Folder 691)
    - Baptist Missionary Hospital (English) - Sianfu, 1921-25 (Box 33, Folder 692)
    - Baptist Missionary Hospital (English) - Taiyuanfu, 1920-24 (Box 33, Folder 693)
    - A. H. Barber, 1919 (Box 33, Folder 694)